Hi, my name's Abby, and today I'm going
to be teaching you how to do a back
walkover. So, I'll just show you how
that looks.
Okay, just to break it down, we're going
to start to the side with our right leg
in tondu devant here. If you're a lefty,
you can go ahead and do your left leg,
but I'm just going to show you the right
today. We're going to start with our
arms by our ears. We're going to reach
back to the floor. We want to make sure
our eyes are trying to find the floor
and that our ears are our arms stay
connected to our ears the entire time.
We're going to reach back into a back
bend position as our right leg comes to
the air. When our hands touch the floor,
we're going to push off this foot super
hard so that we can make sure to get
that good split position during our back
walkover. It is key that we have two
straight legs. It'll make it a lot
prettier. You'll be able to hit that
split, and then you're going to step out
of it to land in tondu again. I'll show
that one more time.